roadplan.com 2014-04-27

# RoadPlan.com | Privacy Policy

We know how important your privacy is to you when surfing the Internet because it's important to us too. Throughout this privacy policy, we will explain how your information is being used and what precautions we have taken to protect your personal information. By using Road Plan you agree to the terms and conditions outlined below.

We may make changes to this policy at any time. If any changes are made to the policy, the most updated version will be displayed on this page. Any questions or comments you have regarding this policy, please visit our Contact Us page.

**Information We Collect**  
We collect both personal identifiable and not personal identifiable information from our users. The personal information we collect includes your name and login information, which you will use to access your account. The not personal identifiable information we collect includes your IP address, browser type, and search statistics.

Road Plan wants to provide each of our users with a personalized experience while browsing our site. With our specialized login system, we can deliver our users customer service and content that is better targeted to their needs. When registering on Road Plan, each user will be asked his or her first and last name along with their email address.

Any information posted by you on Road Plan can be displayed publicly on our website. Once you submit information on our site we have the authority to use it for site improvement and marketing purposes. As a reminder do not include any information in your submissions that you want kept private.

**Protecting Your Information**  
Strong security measures have been put in place to safeguard your information.

Road Plan will never sell, rent, or trade your information to a third party. Although third party advertisements are displayed on Road Plan, we are not affiliated, and cannot be held accountable for your privacy once you leave our site. To ensure your safety be sure to read the privacy policies on all the sites you visit.

Road Plan reserves the option to share information with our current and future affiliates. These affiliates include our: parent company, joint ventures, subsidiaries, or companies that are under common control. All of the information shared with affiliates is non-personal information and cannot identify you individually.

Your personal information will only be released if it is required to by means of the law including, but not limited to: subpoenas, court orders, warrants or to protect the safety of our users or the public.

**California Online Protection Act**  
Road Plan wants to do our part in reducing identity left. In order to support this movement, we comply with California Online Privacy Protection Act. Your personal information will never be given to a third-party without your consent.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**  
Keeping children safe on the Internet is extremely important to us. Because of this, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Under COPPA, we will never knowingly collect information from a user under the age of 13. Road Plan is intended for those over the age of 13. Please do not use Road Plan if you are under the age of 13 without help from a parent or guardian.

**Unsubscribing From Road Plan**  
We hope you enjoy interacting with our site. However, we realize the choice to continue communication with our site is up to you. If at any time you decide to discontinue communication with Road Plan, visit our Unsubscribe page at: <http://www.roadplan.com/unsubscribe>.
